<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
    <title>boardagain</title>
    <link href="https://www.boardagain.co.uk/feed.xml" rel="self" />
    <link href="https://www.boardagain.co.uk" />
    <updated>2026-02-10T13:21:10+00:00</updated>
    <author>
        <name>Somerset</name>
    </author>
    <id>https://www.boardagain.co.uk</id>

    <entry>
        <title>Who we are. </title>
        <author>
            <name>IRB</name>
        </author>
        <link href="https://www.boardagain.co.uk/who-we-are.html"/>
        <id>https://www.boardagain.co.uk/who-we-are.html</id>
        <media:content url="https://www.boardagain.co.uk/media/posts/6/4-hands.jpg" medium="image" />

        <updated>2026-02-09T20:38:40+00:00</updated>
            <summary type="html">
                <![CDATA[
                        <img src="https://www.boardagain.co.uk/media/posts/6/4-hands.jpg" alt="" />
                    Board Again is the hypothetical company created by four 14–15-year-old students in Somerset. Our company idea aims to tackle the vast amounts of dry,&hellip;
                ]]>
            </summary>
        <content type="html">
            <![CDATA[
                    <p><img src="https://www.boardagain.co.uk/media/posts/6/4-hands.jpg" class="type:primaryImage" alt="" /></p>
                <p><strong>Board Again is the hypothetical company created by four 14–15-year-old students in Somerset. Our company idea aims to tackle the vast amounts of dry, cardboard waste produced in commercial spaces like shopping centres to small businesses on the Highstreet. Our idea is to take this waste and do 3 things with it: </strong></p>
<p><em><u>-Turn it into cheap but durable furniture.</u></em> We understand that many people in our communities’ face poverty daily in many ways. These people deserve to have a happy functional home but sometimes that can be hard when all your money and time goes to food, rent and looking after family. By providing these communities with furniture like chairs and bookshelves it can make a house a much happier place to live. Everyone deserves this, regardless of income. </p>
<p><em><u>-Remake into paper</u></em>. The process of turning cardboard into paper is a fairly simple process that requires very minimal energy and produces minimal waste on itself. Paper made in this way often has interesting textures or feel to it and can by dyed in many ways naturally. It also happens to be thicker, which is perfect for sketchbooks and notebooks.  </p>
<p><em><u>-Working with the community to learn about sustainability.</u></em> Making paper is such a fun prosses as its not super complicated and can be done on a large or small scale. We would like to work with primary schools, bringing small groups of students into our space to do paper making workshops where they will learn about both sustainability and creativity. We would also encourage them to bring in dry cardboard waste to turn into paper and by having a tangible object at the end it really encourages children to think about waste and how its dealt with at an age-appropriate level, but at the same time learn that they can have an effect even at a small level.</p>
<p><strong>-Our aim. Although this company is hypothetical, our aim with it is not to reduce the amount of cardboard produced as we understand that cardboard is needed for many things and it would be futile to try. We want to take this waste and do something meaningful with it for both the environment and community. </strong></p>
            ]]>
        </content>
    </entry>
</feed>
